Hilpert, Elmer E. Arbitration Papers 5493
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Mallinckrodt Chemical Works, St. Louis, Missouri vs. Independent Union of Chemical Plant Workers., 1961 (Box 60, Folder 4)
  12/22/61. Issue: overtime - schedules of work.
- Mallinckrodt Chemical Works, St. Louis, Missouri vs. Independent Union of Chemical Plant Workers., 1962 (Box 60, Folder 5)
  3/9/62. Issue: assignment of jobs
- Mallinckrodt Chemical Works, St. Louis, Missouri vs. Independent Union of Chemical Plant Workers., 1962 (Box 60, Folder 6)
  4/7/62. Issue: working conditions - wash-up time
- Mallinckrodt Chemical Works, St. Louis, Missouri vs. Independent Union of Chemical Plant Workers., 1962 (Box 60, Folder 7)
  4/12/62. Issue: transfer - temporary
- Mallinckrodt Chemical Works, St. Louis, Missouri vs. Independent Union of Chemical Plant Workers., 1962 (Box 60, Folder 8)
  4/20/62. Issue: overtime
- Mallinckrodt Chemical Works, St. Louis, Missouri vs. Independent Union of Chemical Plant Workers., 1962 (Box 60, Folder 9)
  5/20/62. Issue: working conditions - wash-up time
- Mallinckrodt Chemical Works, St. Louis, Missouri vs. Independent Union of Chemical Plant Workers., 1963 (Box 60, Folder 10)
  3/27/63. Issue: classification of jobs - duties performed
- Mallinckrodt Chemical Works, St. Louis, Missouri vs. Independent Union of Chemical Plant Workers, 1963 (Box 60, Folder 11)
  4/15/63. Issue: assignment of jobs - overtime
- Mallinckrodt Chemical Works, St. Louis, Missouri vs. Independent Union of Atomic Workers, 1964 (Box 60, Folder 12)
  3/10/64. Issue: overtime - assignment of jobs
- Mallinckrodt Chemical Works, St. Louis, Missouri vs. Independent Union of Chemical Plant Workers., 1964 (Box 61, Folder 1)
  9/25/64. Issue: assignment of jobs - de Minimus assignment
- Mallinckrodt Chemical Works, St. Louis, Missouri vs. Independent Union of Chemical Plant Workers., 1969 (Box 61, Folder 2)
  5/27/69. Issue: overtime -assignment of jobs.
- Mallinckrodt Chemical Works, St. Louis, Missouri vs. Independent Union of Chemical Plant Workers., 1956 (Box 61, Folder 3)
  11/9/56. Issue: overtime
- Mallory, P. R., and Co., Inc., Du Quoin, Illinois. vs. IAM, Local, 111, 1958 (Box 61, Folder 4)
  5/30/58. Issue: discipline - discharge.
- Mallory, P. R., and Co., Inc., Du Quoin, Illinois. vs. IAM, Local, 111, 1958 (Box 61, Folder 5)
  5/30/58. Issue: discipline - discharge
- Mallory, P. R., and Co., Inc., Indianapolis, Indiana vs. IUE, Local 1001, 1965 (Box 61, Folder 6)
  12/21/65. Issue: reduction in workforce - layoff.
- Marlo Coil Co. vs. BBF, Lodge 27, 1959 (Box 61, Folder 7-8)
  10/15/59. Issue: discipline - discharge
- Martin-Marietta Corp., Martin Co. Division vs. UAW, Local 766, 1967 (Box 61, Folder 9)
  9/25/67. Issue: assignment of jobs.
- Martin-Marietta Corp., Martin Co. Division vs. UAW, Local 766, 1967 (Box 61, Folder 10)
  9/29/67. Issue: assignment of jobs
- Martin-Marietta Corp., Martin Co. Division vs. UAW, Local 766, 1967 (Box 61, Folder 11)
  9/27/67. Issue: assignment of jobs
- Mason City Brick and Tile Co. vs. United Glass and Ceramic Workers of North America, Local 105, 1963 (Box 61, Folder 12)
  1/10/63. Issue: discipline - discharge.
- Masonite Corp., Laurel, Mississippi vs. IWA, Local 5-443, 1970 (Box 61, Folder 13-14)
  5/4/70. Issue: discipline - discharge.
- Math, Hermann and Son, Inc. vs. Miscellaneous Drivers and Helpers Union, IBT, Local 610, 1974 (Box 61, Folder 15)
  10/28/74. No decision
- McCabe-Powers Auto Body Co. vs. USA, Local 4368, 1950 (Box 61, Folder 16)
  12/27/50. Issue: discipline - discharge.
- McCabe-Powers Auto Body Co. vs. USA, Local 4368, 1955 (Box 61, Folder 17)
  9/20/55. Issue: classification of jobs - promotions
- McCabe-Powers Auto Body Co. vs. USA, Local 4368, 1962 (Box 61, Folder 18)
  6/8/62. Issue: recall - seniority
- McCabe-Powers Auto Body Co. vs. USA, Local 4368, 1966 (Box 61, Folder 19)
  7/26/66. Issue: discipline - discharge
- McCabe-Powers Body Co. vs. USA, Local 4368., 1969 (Box 62, Folder 1)
  5/9/69. Issue: discipline - discharge - absences - notice
- McCoy-Couch Furniture Manufacturing Co. vs. UFWA, Local 268, 1953 (Box 62, Folder 2)
  10/2/53. Issue: termination of employment - inability
- McCoy-Couch Furniture Manufacturing Co. vs. UFWA, Local 268, 1953 (Box 62, Folder 3)
  10/2/53. Issue: termination of employment - time clock procedure
- McCoy-Couch Furniture Manufacturing Co. vs. UFWA, Local 268, 1953 (Box 62, Folder 4)
  10/2/53. Issue: assignment of jobs - seniority.
- McCoy-Couch Furniture Manufacturing Co. vs. UFWA, Local 268, 1953 (Box 62, Folder 5)
  10/2/53. Issue: termination of employment - leaves of absence
- McCoy-Couch Furniture Manufacturing Co. vs. UFWA, Local 268, 1953 (Box 62, Folder 6)
  10/2/53. Issue: vacation pay
- McDonald Construction Co. vs. Int'l. Hod Carriers', Building and Common Laborers' Union, Local 718, 1961 (Box 62, Folder 7)
  7/12/61. Issue: management rights - vacancies
- McConnell Aircraft Corp. vs. United Plant Guard Workers of America, Local 250, 1957 (Box 62, Folder 8)
  7/21/57. Issue: discipline - discharge - alcoholism
- McDonnell Aircraft Corp. vs. IBT, Local 610, 1959 (Box 62, Folder 9)
  3/10/59. Issue: assignment of jobs - bargaining unit work.
- McDonnell-Douglas Aircraft Corp vs. IBT, Local 610, 1968 (Box 62, Folder 10)
  4/15/68. Issue: assignment of jobs
- McDonnell-Douglas Aircraft Corp vs. IBT, Local 610, 1969 (Box 62, Folder 11)
  7/9/69. Issue: assignment of jobs - outside bargaining unit
- McDonnell-Douglas Aircraft Corp vs. IBT, Local 610, 1973 (Box 62, Folder 12)
  3/30/73. Issue: discipline - discharge - misconduct
- McQuay-Norris Manufacturing Co. vs. UAW, Local 231, 1964 (Box 62, Folder 13)
  10/10/64. Issue: termination of employment -sick leave
- Mead Corp. vs. UMW, District 50, 1966 (Box 62, Folder 14)
  4/28/66. Issue: overtime - assignment of jobs
- Mead Corp. vs. Int'l. Brotherhood of Pulp, Sulphite and Paper Mill Workers, Local 988, 1968 (Box 62, Folder 15)
  1/8/68. Issue: vacancies - method of filling
- Memphis, City of, Tennessee vs. AFSCME, Local 1733, 1971 (Box 62, Folder 16)
  8/8/71. Issue: rates of pay
- Memphis and Shelby County Hospital Authority vs. AFSCME, Local 1733, 1973 (Box 62, Folder 17)
  6/22/73. Issue: rates of pay - claim for pay of higher classification.
- Men and Management Conference, Management Division vs. Int'l. Brotherhood of Bookbinders, Local 18, 1953 (Box 62, Folder 18)
  9/23/53. Issue: rates of pay; vacation.
- Mendenhall Motor Co. vs. IBT, Local 604, 1957 (Box 62, Folder 19)
  6/17/57. Issue: discipline - discharge - misconduct
- Meramec Mining Co. vs. USA, Local 5790, 1962 (Box 62, Folder 20)
  4/16/62. Issue: rates of pay
- Meramec Mining Co. vs. USA, Local 5790, 1968 (Box 63, Folder 1)
  4/25/68. Withdrawn
- Meramec Mining Co. vs. USA, Local 5790, 1968 (Box 63, Folder 2-4)
  11/15/68. Issue: classification of jobs - rates of pay
- Merchants' Exchange of St. Louis vs. Int'l. Brotherhood of Longshoremen, Local 1642, 1958 (Box 63, Folder 5)
  6/5/58. Issue: classification of jobs - management rights
- Meredith Corp, 1968 (Box 63, Folder 6)
  11/20/68. No decision
- Mesker Brothers Iron Co. vs. USA, Local 1065, 1956 (Box 63, Folder 7)
  3/1/56. Issue: layoff
- Metal Goods Corp. vs. IBT, Local 688, 1966 (Box 63, Folder 8)
  9/1/66. No decision
- Metro Glass Co., Carteret, New Jersey vs. GBBA, Local 111, 1969 (Box 63, Folder 9)
  12/23/69. Issue: discipline - discharge.
- Metropolitan Life Insurance Co. vs. IWIU, 1961 (Box 63, Folder 10-12)
  5/31/61. Issue: discipline - discharge
- Midwest Handbag Co. vs. TWUA, Local 1340, 1964 (Box 63, Folder 13)
  12/29/64. Issue: rates of pay - minimum wage law, effect
- Midwest Rubber Reclaiming Co. vs. URW, Local 42, 1954 (Box 63, Folder 14)
  4/3/54. Issue: reduction in force - assignment of jobs
- Midwest Rubber Reclaiming Co. vs. URW, Local 42, 1959 (Box 63, Folder 15)
  5/15/59. Issue: assignment of jobs - seniority.
- Midwest Rubber Reclaiming Co. vs. URW, Local 42, 1960 (Box 63, Folder 16)
  12/3/60. Issue: promotions - seniority
- Midwest Rubber Reclaiming Co. vs. URW, Local 42, 1967 (Box 63, Folder 17)
  5/19/67. Issue: posting
- Milprint, Inc. vs. UPP, Local 356, 1959 (Box 63, Folder 18)
  2/28/59. Issue: layoff - temporary.
- Milprint, Inc. vs. UPP, Local 356, 1960 (Box 63, Folder 19)
  8/27/60. Issue: discipline - union representatives
- Milprint, Inc. vs. UPP, Local 1203, 1961 (Box 63, Folder 20)
  10/25/61. Issue: supervisors and foremen - management control over
- Milwaukee and Suburban Transport Co. vs. Amalgamated Association of Street Electric Railway and Motor Coach Employees of America, Division 998, 1955 (Box 63, Folder 21)
  3/2/55. Issue: assignment of jobs - rates of pay
- Milwaukee Boiler Manufacturing Co. vs. UAW, Local 1092, 1961 (Box 64, Folder 1)
  7/15/61. Issue: union representatives and business
- Minerva Oil Co., Mine No. 1, Eldorado, Illinois vs. UMW, Local 12,681, 1959 (Box 64, Folder 2)
  9/18/59. Issue: layoff - seniority
- Minerva Oil Co., Mine No. 1, Eldorado, Illinois vs. UMW, Local 12,681, 1959 (Box 64, Folder 3)
  9/20/59. Issue: layoff - seniority
- Minerva Oil Co., Crystal Mine and Mill, Eldorado, Illinois vs. UMW, Local 12,568, 1959 (Box 64, Folder 4)
  9/21/59. Issue: holidays and holiday pay
- Minerva Oil Co., Cave-In-Rock, Illinois vs. UMW, Local 12,681, 1960 (Box 64, Folder 5)
  8/23/60. Issue: holidays and holiday pay.
- Mississippi Lime Co. of Missouri vs. Int'l. Union of Mine, Mill and Smelter Workers, Ste. Genevieve Lime Workers, Local 883, 1951 (Box 64, Folder 6)
  7/3/51. Issue: overtime.
- Mississippi Lime Co. of Missouri vs. United Glass and Ceramic Workers of North America, Local 169, 1959 (Box 64, Folder 7)
  3/15, 17, 18/59. Issue: arbitrability; rates of pay; working conditions - crew size
- Missouri Portland Cement Co. vs. CLGW, Local 19, 1957 (Box 64, Folder 8)
  1/10/57. Issue: discipline - discharge.
- Missouri Portland Cement Co. vs. CLGW, Local 19, 1958 (Box 64, Folder 9)
  3/25/58. Issue: reduction in force - seniority.
- Missouri Portland Cement Co., Joppa, Illinois vs. CLGW, Local 438, 1966 (Box 64, Folder 10)
  5/14/66. Issue: rates of pay.
- Missouri Public Service Co. vs. IBEW, Local 814, 1961 (Box 64, Folder 11)
  4/8/61. Issue: rates of pay - increase.
- Mobil Oil Co., Socony, East St. Louis, Illinois vs. OCAW, Local 7-644, 1956 (Box 64, Folder 12)
  6/19/56. Issue: vacancies, temporary.
- Mobil Oil Co., Socony, East St. Louis, Illinois vs. OCAW, Local 7-644, 1958 (Box 64, Folder 13)
  11/23/58. Issue: overtime
- Mobil Oil Co., Socony, East St. Louis, Illinois vs. OCAW, Local 7-644, 1959 (Box 64, Folder 14)
  7/10/59. Issue: overtime
- Mobil Oil Co., Socony, East St. Louis, Illinois vs. OCAW, Local 7-644, 1960 (Box 64, Folder 15)
  2/14/60. Issue: vacancies - promotions
- Mobil Oil Co., Socony, East St. Louis, Illinois vs. OCAW, Local 7-644, 1961 (Box 64, Folder 16)
  5/7/61. Issue: assignment of jobs
- Mobil Oil Co., Socony, East St. Louis, Illinois vs. OCAW, Local 7-644, 1961 (Box 64, Folder 17)
- Mobil Oil Co., Socony, East St. Louis, Illinois vs. OCAW, Local 7-644, 1964 (Box 64, Folder 18)
  6/18/64. Issue: discipline - suspensions
- Mobil Oil Co., Socony, East St. Louis, Illinois vs. OCAW, Local 7-644, 1966 (Box 64, Folder 19)
  3/15/66. Withdrawn
- Mobil Oil Co., Socony, East St. Louis, Illinois vs. OCAW, Local 7-644, 1958 (Box 64, Folder 20)
- Mobil Oil Co., Socony, East St. Louis, Illinois vs. OCAW, Local 7-644, 1959 (Box 64, Folder 21)
- Mobil Oil Co., Socony, Kansas City Division vs. Automotive, Petroleum, and Allied Industries Employees Union, Local 618, 1968 (Box 64, Folder 22)
  9/3/68. Issue: holiday pay; vacation pay
- Mobile Plywoods, Inc. vs. General Drivers and Helpers Union, IBT, Local 354, 1972 (Box 64, Folder 23)
  8/8/72. Issue: management rights - contracting out
- Mohawk Rubber Co. vs. URW, Local 539., 1974 (Box 64, Folder 24-25)
  12/10/74. Issue: discharge - slowdown, participation. (Continued in Box 65.)
- Mohawk Rubber Co. vs. URW, Local 539., 1974 (Box 65, Folder 1-5)
  12/10/74. Issue: discharge - slowdown, participation. (Continued from Box 64.)
- Mohr's Restaurant vs. Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders Int'l. Union (HREU), Local 117, 1956 (Box 65, Folder 6)
  6/28/56. Issue: rates of pay.
- Monsanto Co. vs. OCAW, Local 5-434, 1966 (Box 65, Folder 7)
  5/11/66. Case deferred
- Monsanto Chemical Co. vs. ICW, Local 16, 1949 (Box 65, Folder 8)
  7/20/49. Issue: union security - maintenance of membership
- Monsanto Chemical Co. vs. ICW, Local 16, 1951 (Box 65, Folder 9)
  8/27/51. Issue: disability - reinstatement
- Monsanto Chemical Co. vs. ICW, Local 16, 1955 (Box 65, Folder 10)
  11/3/55. Issue: discipline - discharge - dishonesty
- Monsanto Chemical Co. vs. ICW, Local 12, 1957 (Box 65, Folder 11)
  2/21/57. Issue: assignment of jobs - new product
- Montgomery Manufacturing Co. vs. USA, Local 5343, 1968 (Box 65, Folder 12)
  5/14/68. Issue: layoff
- Moog Industries vs. UAW, Local 282, 1972 (Box 65, Folder 13)
  12/12/72. Issue: termination of employment - sick leave
- Moran Inland Waterways Corp vs. MMP, Local 28, 1958 (Box 66, Folder 1)
  6/2/58. Issue: discipline - discharge - carelessness and negligence
- Morgan, Arthur, Trucking Co. vs. IBT, Local 682, 1961 (Box 66, Folder 2)
  9/26/61. Issue: discipline - discharge - insubordination
- Morgan, Wm., and Cecil Cary vs. USA, Local 3001, 1950 (Box 66, Folder 3)
  10/11/50. Issue: seniority
- Morris Paint and Varnish Co. vs. Paint Makers and Warehousemen Union, Local 604, 1961 (Box 66, Folder 4)
  10/28/61. Issue: discipline - discharge - unsatisfactory work
- Mosstie Co. vs. UMW, District 50, 1963 (Box 66, Folder 5)
  11/14/63. Issue: seniority.
- Moss-American Inc. vs. UMW, District 50, Local 15,108, 1965 (Box 66, Folder 6)
  11/14/65. Issue: discipline - discharge - insubordination
- Motor Carriers' Council of St. Louis vs. IBT, Local 632, 1952 (Box 66, Folder 7)
  4/26/52. Issue: discipline - discharge - absences
- Motor Carriers' Council of St. Louis vs. IBT, Local 600, 1953 (Box 66, Folder 8)
  1/5/53. Issue: discipline - layoff - carelessness and negligence
- Motor Carriers' Council of St. Louis vs. IBT, Local 600, 1953 (Box 66, Folder 9)
  3/18/53. Issue: discipline - layoff - carelessness
- Motor Carriers' Council of St. Louis vs. IBT, Local 632, 1953 (Box 66, Folder 10)
  3/24/53. Issue: holiday pay
- Motor Carriers' Council of St. Louis vs. IBT, Local 632, 1953 (Box 66, Folder 11)
  7/1/53. Issue: assignment of jobs - added duties
- Motor Carriers' Council of St. Louis vs. IBT, Local 688, 1960 (Box 66, Folder 12)
  11/19/60. Issue; fringe benefits - bonuses.
- Motor Carriers' Council of St. Louis vs. IBT, Local 688, 1960 (Box 66, Folder 13)
  11/16/60. Issue: overtime - computation of
- Mueller Co. vs. AIW, Local 838, 1969 (Box 66, Folder 14)
  1/23, 26/69. Issue: shift scheduling; overtime
- Murphy, G. W., Industries, Inc. vs. USA, Local 2083, 1972 (Box 66, Folder 15)
  8/26/72. Issue: rates of pay
- Nashville Bridge Co. vs. Shopmen's Union, Local 733, 1966 (Box 66, Folder 16)
  12/21/66. No award
- National Dairy Products Corp. vs. GBBA, Local 111, 1966 (Box 66, Folder 17-18)
  6/6/66. Issue: discipline - discharge.
- National Dairy Products Corp. - Sealest Div. vs. IBT, Local 729, 1962 (Box 67, Folder 1)
  1/6/62. Issue: rates of pay; management rights - reduction in force
- National Distillers and Chemical Corp. vs. IUOE, Local 515, 1961 (Box 67, Folder 2)
  6/12/61. Issue: classification of jobs - new job
- National Distillers and Chemical Corp. vs. IUOE, Local 515, 1961 (Box 67, Folder 3)
  8/7/61. Issue: discipline - discharge - alcoholism - improper personal conduct
- National Distillers and Chemical Corp. vs. IUOE, Local 515, 1964 (Box 67, Folder 4)
  6/28/64. Issue: rates of pay - overtime - emergency assignment
- National Food Stores, Inc. vs. RCIA, Local 344., 1967 (Box 67, Folder 5)
  7/17/67. Issue: discipline - discharge - theft.
- National Lead Co. vs. OCAW, Local 8-107, 1958 (Box 67, Folder 6)
  3/24/58. Issue: layoff -health insurance
- National Lead Co. vs. Brotherhood of Painters, Decorators and Paperhangers of America, Local 1952, 1969 (Box 67, Folder 7)
  11/3/69. Issue: shift scheduling - vacancies.
- National Lead Co. vs. Lead Workers Federal Labor Union, Local 22,765, 1957 (Box 67, Folder 8)
  10/29/57. Issue: call back pay.
- National Lead Co. vs. USA, Local 1989, 1962 (Box 67, Folder 9)
  7/9/62. Issue: assignment of work outside bargaining unit
- National Lead Co. vs. USA, Local 1989, 1968 (Box 67, Folder 10)
  9/23/68. Issue: discharge - absences - unauthorized - notice
- N. L. Industries, Inc. vs. Chemical Workers Basic Union, Local 1744, 1973 (Box 67, Folder 11)
  7/14/73. Issue: layoff - vacation pay
- National Lead Co. vs. Fernald AFL-CIO Atomic Trades and Labor Council, 1968 (Box 67, Folder 12)
  8/31/68. Issue: claim for pay of a higher classification - trainees.
- National Marine Service, Inc. vs. BBF, AFL-CIO, Local 363, 1975 (Box 67, Folder 13)
  3/25/75. Issue: disciplinary discharge and suspensions - strike misconduct and misappropriation
- National Oats Co. vs. AFGM, Local 167, 1954 (Box 67, Folder 14)
  10/12/54. Issue: overtime - equalization, seniority
- National Oats Co. vs. IUOE, Local 149, 1969 (Box 67, Folder 15)
  5/9/69. Issue: failure to schedule overtime
- National Potash Co. vs. United Stone and Allied Products Workers of America, Local 177, 1961 (Box 67, Folder 16)
  8/12/61. Issue: failure to call-in; overtime.
- National Starch and Chemical Corp. vs. BBF, Local 363, 1975 (Box 67, Folder 17)
  2/14/75. Issue: cost of living allowance.
- Nesco Steel Barrel Co. vs. USA, Local 1021, 1973 (Box 67, Folder 18)
  5/5/73. Issue: discharge - absence - reporting
- Nestle Co. vs. Federal Labor Union, Coffee Processors, Local 24,562, 1956 (Box 68, Folder 1)
  7/16/56. Issue: discipline - discharge - failure to call-in
- Niedringhaus Metal Products Co. vs. USA, Local 1622, 1951 (Box 68, Folder 2)
  1/8/51. Issue: discipline - discharge.
- Niedringhaus Metal Products Co. vs. USA, Local 1622, 1963 (Box 68, Folder 3)
  9/30/63. Issue: fringe benefits - pension plans.
- Noranda Aluminum, Inc. vs. USA, Local 7686, 1973 (Box 68, Folder 4)
  8/5/73. Issue: arbitrability; discipline - discharge - breach of no strike clause
- Oldberg Manufacturing Co. vs. UAW, Local 742, 1966 (Box 68, Folder 5)
  5/18/66. Withdrawn
- Olin Mathieson Chemical Corp. vs. Western Employees' Trades Council, 1964 (Box 68, Folder 6)
  9/18/64. Issue: assignment of jobs - seniority
- Olin Mathieson Chemical Corp. vs. AIW, Local 437, 1968 (Box 68, Folder 7)
  12/5/68. Issue: arbitration procedure - multiple grievances
- Olinkraft, Inc. vs. Int'l. Brotherhood of Pulp, Sulphite and Paper Mill Workers, Local 752, 1968 (Box 68, Folder 8)
  3/25/68. Issue: arbitrability; promotions - seniority
- Ontario Foods of St. Louis, Inc. vs. MCBW, AFL-CIO, Local 88, 1973 (Box 69, Folder 1)
  6/30/73. Issue: discharge, improper personal conduct - quarrelsome and uncooperative
- Owens-Illinois Glass Co. vs. American Flint Glass Workers' Union (AFGW), Local 43, 1960 (Box 69, Folder 2)
  12/12/60. Issue: retirement - compulsory
- Owens-Illinois Glass Co. vs. GBBA, Local 24, 1962 (Box 69, Folder 3)
  11/18/62. Issue: discharge - leaving work area without permission
- Owens-Illinois, Inc., Glass Container Manufacturers Institute vs. GBBA, 1966 (Box 69, Folder 4)
  9/29/66. No award - matter held in abeyance
- Owens-Illinois, Inc., Glass Container Manufacturers Institute, Inc. vs. GBBA, Local 95., 1969 (Box 69, Folder 5)
  4/14/69. Issue: strike - payment of wages for lost time
- Owens-Illinois, Inc., GCMI vs. GBBA, Local 40, 1970 (Box 69, Folder 6)
  5/7/70. Issue: elimination of job
- Owens-Illinois, Inc., GMCI vs. GBBA, 1966 (Box 69, Folder 7)
  1/6/66. Matter held in abeyance - no award
- Owens-Illinois, Inc., GMCI vs. GBBA, 1969 (Box 69, Folder 8)
  8/19/69. Settled
- Owens-Illinois, Inc., GMCI vs. GBBA, Local 101, 1969 (Box 69, Folder 9)
  12/12/69. Issue: discharges - improper personal conduct - fighting
- Owens-Illinois, Inc., GMCI vs. GBBA, Local 101, 1970 (Box 69, Folder 10)
  5/15/70. Issue: layoff - temporary - notice.
- Owens-Illinois Glass Co. vs. GBBA, Local 240, 1965 (Box 69, Folder 11)
  1/21/65. Issue: job classification - upgrading
- Owens-Illinois, Inc., GMCI vs. GBBA, 1969 (Box 69, Folder 12)
  3/26/69. Hearing cancelled
- Owens-Illinois, Inc. vs. GBBA, 1970 (Box 69, Folder 13)
  7/1/70. Withdrawn
- Owens-Illinois, Inc. vs. USA, Local 6936, 1969 (Box 69, Folder 14)
  6/26/69. Issue: discharge and disciplinary layoff - wildcat strike
- Owens-Illinois Glass Co. vs. USA, Local 5109, 1962 (Box 69, Folder 15)
  12/8/62. Issue: overtime - call-in
- Owens-Illinois Glass Co. vs. USA, Local 5109, 1964 (Box 69, Folder 16)
  10/14/64. Issue: overtime - call-in
- Owens-Illinois Glass Co. vs. USA, Local 5109, 1966 (Box 69, Folder 17)
  1/18/66. Issue: discharge - improper personal conduct - carelessness
- Owens-Illinois, Inc. vs. Int'l. Brotherhood of Pulp, Sulphite, and Paper Mill Workers, Local 816, 1971 (Box 69, Folder 18)
  4/26/71. Issue: holiday pay - pyramiding
- Owens-Illinois, Inc. vs. Int'l. Brotherhood of Pulp, Sulphite, and Paper Mill Workers, Local 475, 1973 (Box 69, Folder 19)
  6/2/73. Issue: assignment of jobs - overtime.
- Owens-Illinois, Inc., GCMI vs. GBBA, Local 255, 1969 (Box 69, Folder 20)
  4/26/69. Issue: discharge - fighting
- Owens-Illinois, Inc., GCMI vs. GBBA, Local 137, 1969 (Box 69, Folder 21)
  7/14/69. Issue: vacancies - temporary - posting
- Owens-Illinois, Inc., GCMI vs. GBBA, Local 137 and 29, 1970 (Box 69, Folder 22)
  6/15/70. Issue: holiday schedule.
- Owens-Illinois, Inc. vs. USA, 1969 (Box 69, Folder 23)
  8/19/69. No award.
- Owens-Illinois, Inc., GMCI vs. GBBA, Local 141, 1969 (Box 69, Folder 24)
  8/27/69. Issue: rehiring - seniority.
- Owens-Illinois Glass Co. vs. USA, Local 5109, 1959 (Box 70, Folder 1)
  7/21/59. Issue; assignment of jobs - discrimination, male vs. female assignment
- Owens-Illinois Glass Co. vs. USA, Local 5109, 1962 (Box 70, Folder 2)
  6/21/62. Issue: pre-shift overtime; remedy for improper assignment
- Owens-Illinois, Inc., GCMI vs. GBBA, Local 140, 1967 (Box 70, Folder 3)
  10/17/67. Issue: classification of jobs - evaluation of job factors
- Owens-Illinois, Inc., GCMI vs. GBBA, Local 140, 1967 (Box 70, Folder 4)
  10/17/67. Issue: classification of job - evaluation of job factors
- Owens-Illinois, Inc., GCMI vs. GBBA, Local 3 and 140, 1969 (Box 70, Folder 5)
  8/25/69. Issue: overtime - computation.
- Owens-Illinois, Inc., GCMI vs. GBBA, Local 259, 1970 (Box 70, Folder 6)
  2/27/70. Issue: bidding - posting
- Ozark Border Electric Cooperative vs. IBEW, Local 702, 1971 (Box 70, Folder 7)
  4/28/71. Issue: sick leave - regeneration of benefits
- Ozark-Mahoning Co. vs. UMW, District 50, Local 13,398, 1958 (Box 70, Folder 8)
  2/19/58. Issue: seniority - promotion.
- Ozark-Mahoning Co. vs. UMW, District 50, Local 13,398, 1960 (Box 70, Folder 9)
  3/21/60. Issue: sub-contracting
- Ozark-Mahoning Co. vs. UMW, District 50, Local 13,398, 1960 (Box 70, Folder 10)
  3/23/60. Issue: seniority - overtime
- Ozark-Mahoning Co. vs. UMW, District 50, Local 13,398, 1960 (Box 70, Folder 11)
  3/25/60. Issue: overtime -rate of pay
- Pacific Industries, Inc. - Midland-Wright Division vs. IUE, Local 1000, 1966 (Box 70, Folder 12)
  1/20/66. Settled.
- Pacific Intermountain Express vs. IBT, Local 632, 1951 (Box 70, Folder 13)
  10/22/51. Issue: discharge - refusal of overtime. (With transcript.)
- Packaging Corp. of America vs. UPP, Local 198, 1962 (Box 70, Folder 14)
  6/18/62. Issue: layoff - reduction in force - seniority
- Packwood, G. H., Manufacturing Co. vs. IUE, Local 823, 1965 (Box 70, Folder 15)
  11/7/65. Issue: temporary assignment - seniority